<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Smarter Home Solutions</title>
        <description></description>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 16:47:29 +0100</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 16:47:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v4.0.1</generator>
        
            <item>
                <title>Outdoor Television</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;I have recently bought a hot tub to enjoy the starry nights and to watch the sun go down.  Whilst we wait for delivery (6 months!), I’ve been contemplating exactly where to put it in the garden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife suggested we could put the hot tub in front of the french doors at the rear of our home, which when opened we could watch a TV attached to the back wall of our dining room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I discovered you can buy an outdoor television, I did not know that was even a thing!  And they’re not small too and unlike a living room where you can’t go too big, you are outdoors so bigger is most definitely better!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On further investigation, I’ve found that Amazon actually supply these products!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are going on my wish list!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/product/B08HV747HX/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1634&amp;amp;creative=6738&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B08HV747HX&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=ianakapilotli-21&amp;amp;linkId=a2d89d9b114f40351a1c341be835e4d4&quot;&gt;KUVASONG 55 Inches Sun Readable Smart Outdoor TV for Outdoor Covered Area, High Brightness True 1500 Nits Outdoor Television, 4K UHD, DVB-T2S2, CI+Slot, Built-in 10Wx2 speakers, plus External Soundbar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/product/B08CT9XKVL/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1634&amp;amp;creative=6738&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B08CT9XKVL&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=ianakapilotli-21&amp;amp;linkId=7943d4ec2e44d9f35ddd426fb75ccb18&quot;&gt;KUVASION 43 Inches Ultra Slim All Weather Sun Readable Smart Outdoor TV, High Brightness 2000 Nits, 43 Inches Weatherproof Outdoor TV, Garden TV, Swimming Pool TV, Patio TV, WIFI Wireless Televisions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/outdoor-television</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/outdoor-television</guid>
                
                <category>Television</category>
                
                <category>Hot tub</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Automate your curtains / drapes</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Just before Christmas, I installed two of these robotic curtain opener/closer devices (drapes to our American friends) in less than 30 minutes.  I chose the rod version (track is also available) as our curtains have eyelets and because the curtains open from the middle, I needed two. Ours are configured to work as a pair, so one command and they open/close.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also ordered the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.switch-bot.com/products/switchbot-hub-mini?sca_ref=533876.jGUgXLNUZy&quot;&gt;hub&lt;/a&gt; to enable control via Cloud services like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ifttt.com&quot;&gt;IFTTT.com&lt;/a&gt; and the Amazon Alexa.
Using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ijpuk.com/solutions/read/amazon-alexa-doorbell-skill&quot;&gt;IJPUK.com Alexa Doorbell skill&lt;/a&gt; I can now control the automatic opening and closing of the curtains from my home automation system via their simple API.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s one more thing I don’t have to think about!  Thank you &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.switch-bot.com/products/switchbot-curtain?sca_ref=533876.jGUgXLNUZy&quot;&gt;Switchbot!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/automate-your-curtains-drapes</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/automate-your-curtains-drapes</guid>
                
                <category>Alexa</category>
                
                <category>IJPUK</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>You've got mail</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Remember the film with Meg Ryan and Tom Hanks “You’ve got mail”, well today with the help of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ijpuk.com/solutions/read/amazon-alexa-doorbell-skill&quot;&gt;IJPUK.COM&lt;/a&gt; and their Alexa doorbell skill service whenever the postman delivers the mail, Alexa announces “You’ve got mail”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how&quot;&gt;How?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/20200702220932-IMG_1317.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Door / Window sensor&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the help of a battery-operated door / window sensor stuck to the letterbox and coupled with a home automation controller, which sends a notification to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ijpuk.com/solutions/read/amazon-alexa-doorbell-skill&quot;&gt;IJPUK.COM&lt;/a&gt;, which runs an Alexa routine to make an announcement all around the house which says “You’ve got mail!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easy!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/youve-got-mail</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/youve-got-mail</guid>
                
                <category>Alexa</category>
                
                <category>IJPUK</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Alexa announcing Google Nest Hello</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;So, you have bought a Google Nest Hello doorbell and you want your Alexa device to announce when someone is at the door.  Well, look no further as we have the answer for you on how to connect these differing technological platforms together with what might first appear as some sticky back plastic and card.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-make-this-work-better&quot;&gt;How to make this work better&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The missing ingredients are &lt;a href=&quot;https://ifttt.com&quot;&gt;IFTTT&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ijpuk.com&quot;&gt;IJPUK.COM&lt;/a&gt;, using these simple services will enable you to automatically recognise people and make your Alexa announce who is at the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;steps&quot;&gt;Steps&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create an account on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ijpuk.com&quot;&gt;IJPUK.COM&lt;/a&gt; and link your Amazon Alexa device, once you have got your Amazon Alexa device chiming using the doorbell test facility, then look at the API settings for the doorbell.  From this screen, you will get all the instructions you need for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ifttt.com&quot;&gt;IFTTT&lt;/a&gt; service.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Once you have created an account on &lt;a href=&quot;https://ifttt.com&quot;&gt;IFTTT&lt;/a&gt; then connect to your Nest account, configure it recognise someone and finally set it to call a &lt;del&gt;&lt;em&gt;Webhook&lt;/em&gt;, specify the details as per the configuration settings from the &lt;em&gt;API settings&lt;/em&gt; page from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ijpuk.com&quot;&gt;IJPUK.COM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/del&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ifttt.com/alexa_doorbell&quot;&gt;Alexa Doorbell by IJPUK Solutions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; IFTTT service (so much easier)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All done!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;related-questions&quot;&gt;Related Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Can you use Amazon Alexa as a doorbell?  Yes, using a technology bridging service from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ijpuk.com&quot;&gt;IJPUK.COM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is NEST Hello compatible with Alexa? Yes, Alexa can announce when the doorbell is pressed, see service from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ijpuk.com&quot;&gt;IJPUK.COM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/alexa-announcing-google-nest-hello</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/alexa-announcing-google-nest-hello</guid>
                
                <category>IFTTT</category>
                
                <category>Alexa</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>